本字幕由YYeTs字幕组原创翻译
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
饥饿
的青春
第二季  第五集
翻译  冰蓝  roaddog
校对  roaddog
后期  斯人   总监  roaddog
时间轴  aaaBao
-明天要见面了我好激动  -我也是
- I am so excited to see you tomorrow. - Me too.
我们终于要完善我们的关系了
We're finally going to consummate our relationship!
还要第一次滚床单
And we're gonna have sex for the first time.
说到这里  我拿到性病检测结果咯
Speaking of which, I got my STD test.
你是说"可以做爱"的结果吗
You mean your "Safe To Do It" test?
是啊  我像口哨一样干净
Yup, clean as a whistle,
虽然口哨一点也不干净
though whistles aren't actually very clean at all.
嘴就是有害细菌的港湾
The mouth is a haven for harmful bacteria.
好吧  留在卧室里说吧
All right. Save that for the bedroom.
我下班后去检查  但是别担心
Well, I'm getting my test after work, but don't worry.
自从我上次检测过后  我只跟一个人做过
I've only been with one person since the last time I was tested.
我随便问一下  那人是谁啊
Yeah, and just casually asking, who was that one other guy?
那不重要
Uh... it's not important.
重要的是下次我们在一起时
What is important is the next time we're together,
我们会水乳交融
we're gonna be together.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
虽然对我来说  算上时差
Though for me, with the time change,
所以其实是昨天  我们已经做完爱了
it'll actually be yesterday, in which case, we already had sex.
-怎么样  -超棒
- How were we? -Amazing!
谢谢你  在线技术支持人员
Thank you, online tech support person man.
-好啊  乔什  -加比
- Hello, Josh. - Gabi.
如果你电脑有问题  可以来找我
If you have a computer problem, you can come to me.
就是上一个跟你做爱的人
You know... the last guy you had sex with.
你在偷听我的私人谈话吗
Were you listening to my private conversation?
你是说在我的厨房里  用我的电脑  我的网络
Your private conversation that you were having in my kitchen
-进行的私人谈话吗  -天啊  这很有道理
- with my Internet on my laptop? - My god, that's a good point.
等等  你和库珀在中国待了三周
So wait, you were with Cooper in China for three weeks,
同床共枕  但什么都没干吗
sharing a bed, and nothing?
-我认识你不到三小时就...  -我知道
- I knew you for less than three hours and we-- - I know!
所以我要小心点
That's why I was being careful.
上次跟我做爱的人
I mean, the last person I had sex with,
最后搞得一团糟
it kind of ended up a big mess.
我听到的是
So, what I'm hearing
没人能达到
is that no man could possibly measure up
那个帅哥的标准
to that big... handsome mess.
不  你听到的是我礼貌地询问
No, what you're hearing is me politely asking
我能不能早点下班去诊所
if I can leave work early and go to the clinic.
好让你进行"可以做爱
So you can get your "Safe to do it"
-因为你还没做过"的检查吗  -就是这个
- cause you haven't "Done it yet" test? - Yes, that's the one.
你可以去  但是
Yes, you can go, but look,
你没什么好担心的  我很安全
you have nothing to worry about. I'm safe.
是啊  但你知道俗话说得好
Yeah, you are, but you know how they say
跟一个人上过床
when you have sex with someone,
就等于跟他睡过的所有人上床了
you have sex with everybody they've had sex with?
加比  我跟你上床时唯一
Gabi, the only other person I was sleeping with
另外的床伴就是卡洛琳
when I slept with you was Caroline.
新计划
New plan.
我们都做检查  我打电话给医生
We're both getting tested. I'll call my doctor.
你医生的办公室好棒啊
Your doctor's office is really nice.
在我去的那家诊所
At the clinic that I go to,
如果你进去时没病
if you didn't have something walking in,
那出来时就肯定有病了
you're gonna have something walking out.
你付钱  对吧
You're paying, right?
如果是好消息的话
Only if it's good news!
对不起  我只是很紧张
I'm sorry. I'm just really nervous.
这是我和库珀的第一次
This is mine and Cooper's first time.
天啊  如果我有病怎么办
Oh god! What if I have something?
整个晚上都毁了
That could kill the whole night!
-加比  你没事的  -你又不知道
- Gabi, you're fine. - You don't know that!
我们等了好长时间
I mean, we waited such a long time,
他为酒店房间付了好多钱
and he paid so much for the hotel room.
不是他告诉我的
I mean, not that he told me how much,
而是我上网查的
but I definitely looked it up online.
他想让这一切对我来说很特别
And he's trying to make it so special for me,
我已经买了毕业礼服呢
and I already bought the cap and gown.
毕业礼服吗
Cap and gown?
天啊  你觉得太过了吗
Oh. God, do you think it's too much?
我觉得这会很性感
I thought it'd be really hot
如果我穿着性感的毕业礼服
if I rolled up my test results like a diploma...
像卷毕业证一样卷起我的检测结果
...dress up in a sexy cap and gown,
懂吗  因为我们毕业了
Get it? 'cause we're graduating
进入了我们关系的下一级
to the next level of our relationship--
-性爱级  -我懂
- the sex level. - I get it.
我在想办法忘记
I'm trying to un-get it.
对不起  我话太多了吗
I'm sorry, am I saying too much?
我不知道你是否知道  但我紧张的时候
I don't know if you know this, but when I'm nervous,
-话很多  -是啊  只在你紧张的时候
- I really seem to talk a lot. - Yeah. Only when you're nervous.
好了  我看了你的全血球计数化学-7试验盘
All right, I've looked over your C.B.C. Chem-7 test panel,
还看了性传播感染血清学检查结果
and checked out your S.T.I. serologic test--
天啊  我要死了
Oh my god! I'm dying!
-冷静点  你们都没事  -真好
- Calm down, you're both fine. - Oh good.
我要说一句  你俩一起来
And may I just say, it was really responsible
做测试真是太负责了
for the two of you to come in to be tested together.
我真的希望更多情侣跟你们一样
I really wish more couples were like you.
耶  现在我可以和我男朋友做爱了
Yay! Now I get to go have sex with my boyfriend.
谢谢你  老板
Thanks, boss.
别问
Don't ask.
尤兰达
Oh, Yolanda.
Yolanda?
搞什么啊
What the hell?
我是来拔牙的
I come get my tooth pulled,
醒来后就在走廊上
and I wake up in the hallway
和我的前夫亲热吗  难以置信
making out with my ex-husband? Unbelievable.
是啊
Yes, it is.
加比  你认识科尔曼
Gabi, you know Coleman.
他出轨了  伤了尤兰达的心
He's the guy that broke Yolanda's heart by cheating on her.
一般情况下我会对这事很感兴趣  但是
You know, normally, I'd be eating this up, but...
库珀和我今晚要第一次做爱了
Cooper and I are having sex for the first time tonight,
所以拜拜了
so bye!
拜托  乔什  我们不能重新开始吗
Come on, Josh. Can't we just start over?
如果你是说你和尤兰达  不行
If you mean you and Yolanda, no.
但如果你是说你和我  那也不行
But if you mean you and me, no.
那你有别的原因留在这里吗
Well, then do you have another reason to be here?
没有  拜拜  乔什
No. Bye-bye, Josh.
我们回头谈
We'll talk about this later.
那有点不舒服
That was a little uncomfortable.
-还用说  -是啊
- You're telling me. - Yeah.
我们到哪了
Now where were we?
索菲亚  这是家五星旅馆
Sofia, this is a five-star hotel.
简直全是星啊
That's, like, all of the stars!
别在那傻站着
Well, don't just stand there.
帮我洗劫小冰箱
Help me raid the mini-bar.
我已经帮你拿了洗发水和护发素
I already got the shampoo and condish for ya.
要开始性感起来噜
Things are about to get sexy.
没错
Yes.
-五星级的性感  -是
- A five-star sexy! - Yeah.
这张床真性感
This bed is so sexy.
枕头上放着巧克力
Chocolates on the pillow!
太性感了
Super sexy.
喂
Hello?
是我  从浴室给你打电话呢
It's me, calling you from the bathroom!
我来啦
I'm here!
-你也来了  -天啊
- And you are here. - Oh my god!
这面镜子好棒
There's the coolest mirror in here!
索菲亚也来了
And Sofia's here!
你好  库珀  你俩好好享受吧
Hey, Cooper! Have fun, you two.
我要回去洗头喝小酒了
I'm gonna wash my hair and make tiny drinks.
-等等  让我弄点情调  -好
- Wait, wait, let me set the mood. - Okay.
你记得你喜欢的浪漫电影里
You know how in those romantic movies you like,
-床上总是撒玫瑰花瓣吧  -是的
- there's always rose petals on the bed? - Yeah.
它们该散开落下来的
They were supposed to cascade and flutter,
但我手上太潮了  因为我真的很紧张
but my hands are sweaty, 'cause I'm really nervous.
也许这能让你放松点
Well, maybe this will calm you down.
不不不
No, no, no.
我没撒开花瓣真的那么糟吗
Did I really blow it with the rose-petal clump that bad?
不  我有个惊喜给你  坐下  闭上眼
No, I have a surprise for you. Sit down, close your eyes.
-我不想你偷看  -别担心
- I don't want you to see. - Don't worry.
我眼镜上已经起雾了
My glasses are already fogged up.
好  要开始了
Okay, this is happening.
真的要开始了
This is really happening.
淡定  库珀
Calm down, Cooper.
你也是  小库珀
You too, mini-Cooper.
好了  睁眼吧
Okay, open your eyes.
这比我麻省理工的毕业典礼赞多了
This is so much better than my graduation from M.I.T.
因为没我这么美的姑娘吗
'Cause the girls weren't as pretty?
还有我妈也不在这
And my mother isn't here.
确诊我没有病哦
Proof positive that I am negative.
-你真棒  -而且绝对安全
- You are amazing. - And safe to do it.
-这上面怎么写的"乔什·卡明斯基"  -什么
- Why does this say, "Josh Kaminski"? - What?
他们就是拼不对我的名字
They can never spell my name right!
加比  我是程序员  不擅长跟人打交道
Gabi, I work with computers, so I'm not too good with people,
但我确信你给我
But I'm pretty sure you handing me
乔什的性病检测是有史以来最糟的前戏了
Josh's S.T.D. test results is the worst foreplay ever.
好吧  记得我说过不让你干的那件事吗
Okay, remember that one thing I said I'd never let you do?
你可以干
I'll let you.
加比  怎么回事
Gabi, what's going on?
听着  别慌
Okay, listen, don't freak out,
因为这什么都代表不了
because it meant absolutely nothing.
-天啊  你在跟乔什上床  -上过床
- Oh god, you're sleeping with Josh! - No, slept with.
那都是老早以前的事了
It's like when I got my hair cornrowed?
只发生过一次  我很后悔
It was one time, in the past, and I totally regretted it!
他就是跟你上床的那一个人吗
He's the one guy you had sex with?
那是我做试用晚餐应聘乔什大厨的晚上
It was the night of my trial dinner to be Josh's new chef.
-你是这么应聘上的吗  -不
- That's how you got the job? - No!
我是得到工作以后才跟他上床的
I slept with him after I got the job.
他和卡洛琳刚分手  伤心欲绝
Him and Caroline had just broken up, he was devastated,
我喝醉了...
I was drunk...
是啊  我现在两件事都要干
Yeah, well, I'm about to be both of those things.
好吧  你生气了
Okay. You're mad.
你能化悲愤为激情把我扔床上吗
Can you channel that passion and throw me onto the bed?
我走了
I'm outta here.
库珀  你不能走
Cooper, you can't just leave.
你说得对
You're right.
我坐了十三小时飞机
I spent 13 hours on a plane,
花八百块订下这间漂亮的旅馆套房
paid $800 for this beautiful hotel suite,
还做了男士脱毛
tried a little something called manscaping...
就为了和你共度这奇妙之夜
all so we could have this magical night together.
所以你猜怎么着  我不走
So you know what? I am gonna stay.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
你走
You're leaving.
我羞愧地离开吗
Leaving? In shame?
这简直是我高中毕业重演
This is like my high school graduation all over again,
除了上次  我的确上了床
except that time, I did have sex,
还没拿到毕业证
and I did not get a diploma.
签在这里
Sign there...
这里
and there.
首字母签那里
Initial there.
你就正式成为同志啦
And you are officially gay!
没反应吗  这招一般很成功的
Nothing? That gay stuff usually kills.
抱歉  艾略特  我就是忍不住想
I'm sorry, Elliot, I just can't stop thinking
尤兰达和科尔曼亲热那事
about Yolanda making out with Coleman.
我懂  就像是他掉进了动物园的河马池
I know. It's like he fell into the hippo pit at the zoo,
好不容易爬了出来
managed to escape,
然后又转头跳了进去
and then jumped right back in again!
我知道天很晚  我也下班了
Look, I know it's late and my day off,
所以如果你给我加班工资  我没意见
so if you wanna pay me overtime, go right ahead.
但这不是我来的原因
But that's not why I'm here.
我想聊聊大家心知肚明的那事
I want to talk about the elephant in the room.
房间里的大象
闭嘴  艾略特
Shut up, Elliot!
尤兰达  我知道我只是你老板
Look, Yolanda, I know I'm just your boss,
但每次他劈腿  惹你伤心的时候
but I'm also the boss whose couch you cried on
看到你哭的也是我
every time he cheated on you.
我知道  我想告诉你我和他结束了
I hear you, and I want you to know I ended it with him,
所以我这周末要去纳帕
which is why I'm going to Napa this weekend
和我的朋友们一起
with my girlfriends to drown myself
喝黑皮诺喝到天昏地暗
in a big barrel of pinot noir.
好忘了科尔曼的黑大X
You know, to forget Coleman's pinot noir.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
我觉得这样最好
I really think this is for the best.
不过  你去医生办公室干什么
By the way, what were you doing at the doctor's offce, anyway?
是担心到要跟踪我吗
Were you so worried you were following me?
不是
Uh, no.
加比和我去做性病检测的
Gabi and I were actually getting S.T.D. tests.
拜托  承认吧
Come on, you can admit it.
不  我说真的  看
No, I'm being serious. Look.
加比的维生素D含量好低哦
Gabi's Vitamin D is really low.
-什么  -这是加比的检测结果
- What? - These are Gabi's results.
什么叫"加比的检测结果"
What do you mean, "Gabi's results"?
天啊  我得马上打电话给她
Oh my god, I gotta call her right now.
冷静  亲爱的
Calm down, baby.
那小白妞真要好好晒晒太阳
That little pale girl just needs to get some sun.
这是加比的检测结果  就说明我的结果在她那
These are Gabi's results, which means she has my results,
她要穿上情趣的毕业礼服
and she's gonna dress up all sexy in a cap and gown
把它当成证书交给库珀
and hand 'em to Cooper like a diploma.
人们还觉得同志爱爱奇怪
And people think gay sex is weird.
库珀
Hey, Cooper.
送你们小鸳鸯一瓶香槟哦
A bottle of bubbly for the lovebirds.
加比不在
Gabi's not here...
我看到你检测结果了
and I saw your test results.
怎么样  很棒对吧
How about 'em, huh? Weren't they great?
所以我才给员工人手一份
That's why I gave a copy to my employees.
行了
Stop.
加比什么都说了
Gabi told me everything,
我知道你们上过床
I know you guys had sex together,
很显然你对她有感觉
and obviously you have feelings for her.
-什么  才没有  -这样就说得通了
- What? No, that's so-- - It all makes sense--
为什么我替你工作的时候你不想我们约会
why you didn't want us to date when I was working for you,
为什么你要揍我
why you punched me in the face.
这跟加比没关系  我们是喝多了
That had nothing to do with Gabi. We were drunk.
这里真的人人都拿喝酒当借口
Alcohol really seems to be the excuse for everyone around here.
知道吗  你们真是有病
You know what? You people really have a problem!
库珀  就算我喜欢过她
Cooper, look, even if I were into her,
事实是  她喜欢的是你
the reality is, she's into you.
她总是说起你
She's always talking about you,
和你视频聊天也满面春风
her face lights up during your video chats,
还很激动自己要穿上毕业礼服
and she was so excited to dress up in the cap and gown.
这她也跟你说了吗
She told you about that?
她一紧张话就很多
She talks a lot when she's nervous.
男人之间  你坦白说
Just tell me, man to man...
你喜欢她吗
do you have feelings for her?
如果喜欢  我现在会在这
If I did, would I be here right now,
劝你们两个和好吗
trying to get you two to work things out?
别这样  你喜欢她
Come on, man! You like her,
她喜欢你  去追她吧
she likes you. Go get her.
别教我怎么做
Don't tell me what to do!
我会去追她的  但不是因为你说了
I will go get her. Not because you told me to.
尤兰达
Yolanda?
-乔什  -你不是该在纳帕吗
- Josh! - Aren't you supposed to be at Napa?
不  我说我要睡个小觉
No! I said I was gonna take a napa.
宝贝  怎么走了那么久
Baby, what's taking so long?
那是塔米  她重感冒了
That's Tammy. She's got a nasty cold.
嗓子哑得很
Ooh, throat just raw.
快呀  尤兰达
Come on, Yolanda.
来啊
Bring it.
亲爱的  你还是闭嘴吧
Sweetie, you should stop talking.
开口只能弄得更糟
You're only making it worse.
不  你才弄得更糟
No, you're making it worse.
好吧  塔米就是科尔曼
All right, fine! Tammy's Coleman.
-不是吧  -乔什
- No! - Look, Josh,
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
我该马上了断  跟你走的
I should just end it and leave with you right now.
-没错  我们走  -我不能丢下他
- Exactly. Let's go. - I can't just leave him.
为什么  因为你一点自制力都没吗
Why? Because you have no willpower?
-因为你又爱上他了吗  -不
- Because you're falling for him again? - No!
因为我还把他铐在床头呢
Because he's handcuffed to the headboard.
天啊
Oh my god.
我的胸好大
My boobs are huge!
索菲亚  我为什么不早对库珀坦白乔什的事
God, Sofia, why didn't I tell Cooper about Josh earlier?
因为男生不想听我们过去的情史
Because guys don't want to hear about past hookups.
-他们受不了  -为什么
- They can't handle it. - Why?
我是说  为什么情侣不能像闺蜜一样
I mean, why can't couples be like best friends
无话不谈
and tell each other everything...
就像我们
like us?
-没错  -对  我们就不用担心
- Totally. - Yeah, and we would never have to worry about
骗对方或者有事情瞒着对方
lying or keeping secrets from each other.
绝对的
Total.
天啊  索菲亚  有闺蜜的感觉真好
Oh god, Sofia, it so great having a best friend,
因为无论多难听的事情
'cause no matter if something's hard to hear,
我们都会直说  因为我们相信对方
we just still say it, because we trust each other.
必须的
Totally.
不过  我不是有所指啦
Although-- and I'm not thinking of anything in particular here,
但我们或许也没什么事...
but we might not tell each other...
-都告诉对方  -怎么会
- Everything. - Oh please!
还记得你剪的那个哈莉·贝瑞发型吗
Do you remember your Halle Berry haircut?
是谁跟你说看着活像约翰·雷吉扎莫的
Who told you that it made you look like John Leguizamo?
-你说的  -我为什么要说呢
- You did. - And why would I do that?
因为你爱我  为我好
Because you love me and want the best for me.
没错  换你对我也是一样
That's right, and you would do the same for me.
不论如何  我们都会无话不说
We tell each other everything, no matter what.
这就叫"信任"
It's called "trust."
实际上我或许有件事故意瞒了你
There's actually one thing I might have neglected to tell you,
但说之前我们得喝瓶大的
but we're gonna need the big bottle for that one.
好
Okay.
我等了很久想告诉你这事
I've waited a really long time to tell you this,
天啊  憋死我了
and, god, it's been killing me,
但我发誓我不说的唯一原因
but I swear the only reason I didn't tell you
是因为你和库珀看起来很幸福
was because you seemed so happy with Cooper and...
好吧
okay.
在乔什取消婚礼的那晚
The night that Josh broke off his wedding,
他爬上了逃生梯
he climbed up the fire escape
想告诉你自己喜欢你
to tell you he had feelings for you,
但他看见你和库珀在接吻
but then he saw you kissing Cooper,
他伤心欲绝  然后离开了
and he was devastated, so he left.
当我发现的时候  他要我保守秘密
And then when I found out, he swore me to secrecy.
天啊  我早该告诉你的
Oh god, I should've told you.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
你能原谅我吗
Do you forgive me?
天啊  我的话你根本没听见
Oh my god, you didn't hear a word I said.
对  但我听见了
No, but I did.
我猜猜  加比又把钥匙忘门上了
Well, let me guess. Gabi left her keys in the door again!
库珀  抱歉你是这样知道
Cooper, I'm sorry you had to find out
乔什和加比这事的
about Josh and Gabi this way.
不过是时候让大家知道了
But, you know, it's time everybody knew.
-很显然  大家都知道了  -不  除了加比
- Apparently, everyone did know. - No, not Gabi,
但她醒了以后也会知道
but she's gonna find out as soon as she wakes up,
-因为我不能再瞒着她了  -你说得对
- because I cannot keep this from her anymore. - You're right.
她要知道
She needs to know.
只是  让我告诉她吧
Just... let me be the one to tell her.
-为什么  -我要看见她知道后的表情
- Why? - I need to see her face when she finds out.
只有这样我才能清楚她喜不喜欢乔什
It's the only way I'll know if she has feelings for Josh.
好吧  但是我瞒了她那么久
Okay, but I'm the one that's been keeping this from her,
该做告诉她的那个
so I should be the one to tell her.
你可以住我的旅馆房间
You can stay in my hotel room.
我不觉得...  真的吗
I don't think that-- really?
好吧  但你要告诉她我跟她说了
Okay, but she needs to know that I tried to tell her the truth.
你保证
Promise me you'll tell her.
我保证
I will.
-还有  库珀...  -你可以叫客房服务
- Oh, and, Cooper... - Yes, you can order room service.
-还有...  -还有看一部电影
- And...? - And a movie.
尤兰达赌咒发誓自己不会再见科尔曼了
Yolanda promised up and down she's never gonna see Coleman again,
-我们还来这干什么  -因为尤兰达太软弱
- so why are we at his office? - Because Yolanda is weak.
科尔曼只要打她电话  她就后悔了
All Coleman has to do is call her, and she caves.
所以我们要和科尔曼对质
So we're gonna confront Coleman,
确保他不会再联系她
make sure he never contacts her again.
所以你才要带我来哈
Oh, so that's why you brought me.
我是唱黑脸的  我是动手的
I'm the bad cop! I'm the muscle!
我是用拳头的
I'm the heavy!
我的船鞋上掉了一根穗呢
I'm missing a tassel on my loafer.
科尔曼
Coleman.
-我们得像个男人样聊聊  -像男人
- Look, we need to talk man to man. - To man!
-好吧  -我爱尤兰达
- O-- okay. - I love Yolanda.
我是她同事
And I... work with her.
我们都很关心她
And we both care about her.
好吧  所以有什么问题
Okay, so... what's the problem?
问题是  我们很担心
The problem is, we are worried.
你根本毫无情感
You are emotionally closed off
还拈花惹草
and prone to infidelity.
好了  你悠着点
All right, let's put the tiger back in the cage.
科尔曼...
Coleman, look...
尤兰达看不出来  但她又爱上你了
Yolanda can't see it, but she's falling for you again,
这样很危险
and that's dangerous.
如果你关心她  就别招惹她
So, if you care about her, you gotta leave her alone,
因为只要涉及到你  她就没有自制力
because when it comes to you, she has no self-control.
我当然有
The hell I don't!
只要我想  随时都能跟科尔曼分手
I can end it with Coleman any time I want!
等等  尤兰达
Wait, hold up. Yolanda...
你是又爱上我了吗
are you falling in love with me?
科尔曼
Well, Coleman...
我没想到会这样
I did not see this coming.
这改变了一切
This changes everything.
尤兰达  对不起
Yolanda, I'm sorry.
因为我也又爱上你了
Because I am falling for you again, too.
是吗
You are?
当然
Damn right I am.
我很庆幸自己能有机会补偿你
I'm lucky I get a second chance to make things right.
也正准备这么做
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
因为你插手
Because you butted in,
他们反而感情更好了
they're actually closer than they were before.
谢谢  艾略特
Thank you, Elliot.
我是说  如果你不来这里
I mean, if it wasn't for you coming down here,
他们或许还成不了一对  但你一来
they might not be a couple, but because you did,
-他们成了  -我懂了  艾略特
- they are. - I get it, Elliot.
现在给我出去  好让我来
Now get out, so I can get it.
他们马上要打的那炮
The sex that's about to happen
正是因为你
is because of you.
索菲亚  你的皮肤好嫩哦
Sofia, you have the soft skin of a little girl.
我是库珀  我偶尔保湿的
It's Cooper, and I occasionally moisturize.
库珀  你怎么在这里
Cooper, what are you doing here?
我是说  你在我很高兴  但是...
I mean, I 'm happy you're here, but...
昨晚把你从旅馆赶走我真的很抱歉
I feel horrible that I kicked you out of the hotel room last night.
是啊  那不是我想的
Yeah, that was not the way
我们被赶走的方式
I was hoping we were gonna get kicked out.
是我在吃醋  无理取闹
I was being insecure and irrational.
通常  我只占一样的
Normally, I'm only one of those things.
我也早该跟你说乔什那事的
And I should've told you about Josh.
瞒着你是我不对
It was wrong not to tell you.
我不会再有事骗你了
I will never keep anything from you again.
我也不会  所以我...
Neither will I, which is why...
加比  我有话要跟你说
Gabi, there's something I need to tell you.
我也有话要跟你说
There's something I need to tell you, too.
或许我该先说
Well, maybe I should go first,
因为这真的是大事  我想让你
'cause this is really big, and I really want you
好好消化一下
to take it in before you react.
-我爱你  -什么
- I love you. - What?
抱歉  我等不及了  我爱你
I'm sorry. I couldn't wait. I love you.
你想跟我说什么来着
Now, what did you want to tell me?
我要辞了中国的工作
That I'm quitting my job in China
搬回来和你一起
and moving back to be with you.
是吗
You are?
是的
Yes, of course.
因为我也爱你
Because I love you, too.
太棒了
Yes!
真的很抱歉  我太紧张了
I'm really sorry. I was just really nervous,
因为不确定你是不是会回应我
because I wasn't sure if you were gonna actually say it, too.
-我还有另一个秘密  -什么
- Oh, and I have another secret. - Yeah?
我把旅馆门卡给索菲亚了  家里只剩我们
I gave Sofia the hotel room key, so we're alone.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
天呐
Oh my god.
我懂  是吧
I know. Right?
不  旅馆刚发来了账单
No, the hotel just sent me the bill.
天呐
Oh my god!